Guide to the Washington State University Agricultural Engineering Department Records 1932-1974
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 3. Photographs, 1934-1974.
  - Projects
    - 1177-Self Feeding Silo, 1953-1960; 61 items (Box 9, Folder 272)
    - 1275-Freezing and Cooling of Turkeys, 1954-1956; 11 items (Box 9, Folder 273)
  - All Electric Greenhouse, 1941; 2 items (Box 9, Folder 274)
  - Bean Drying, 1952-1957; 17 items (Box 9, Folder 275)
  - Brooding, 1940-1944; 13 items (Box 9, Folder 276)
  - Brooding Studies, 1946-1959; 68 items (Box 9, Folder 277)
  - Buildings, undated; 16 items (Box 9, Folder 278)
  - Bulk Milk Tank Heat Pump Water Heater, 1955-1958; 21 items (Box 9, Folder 279)
  - Cage Laying House, undated; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 280)
  - Calves
    - Housing, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 281)
    - Pens, 1948; 6 items (Box 9, Folder 282)
  - Chart Negatives, undated; 47 items (Box 9, Folder 283)
  - Experimental Equipment, undated; 16 items (Box 9, Folder 284)
  - Experimental Manger, 1955; 5 items (Box 9, Folder 285)
  - Fair Exhibit Pieces, undated; 3 items (Box 9, Folder 286)
  - Farm Structures
    - Class Project-Veterinary Medicine storage Building, 1952-1956; 20 items (Box 9, Folder 287)
    - Experimental Dairy Group, undated; 6 items (Box 9, Folder 288)
    - Silo, 1949-undated; 34 items (Box 9, Folder 289)
  - Ford Pictures, 1973; 5 items (Box 9, Folder 290)
  - 4-H Smith-Hughes Booklet, Farm Electricity, 1947-undated; 30 items (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Frost Expellers, 1948-1952; 14 items (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - General Photos
    - 1937-1950, 72 items (Box 10, Folder 293)
    - undated, 193 items (Box 10, Folder 294-295)
  - Hartzog (Vocational Agriculture)
    - 1953, 40 items (Box 10, Folder 296)
    - 1954-1956, 60 items (Box 10, Folder 297)
  - Haying Equipment, undated; 10 items (Box 10, Folder 298)
  - Heat Exchangers, 1955; 4 items (Box 10, Folder 299)
  - Heat Lamp, 1955; 14 items (Box 10, Folder 300)
  - Heat Pump, 1953-1958; 19 items (Box 10, Folder 301)
  - High Pressure Spraying, 1949; 3 items (Box 10, Folder 302)
  - House Heating Studies, 1946-1947; 8 items (Box 10, Folder 303)
  - International Harvester, 1959-1974; 82 items (Box 10, Folder 304)
  - Irrigation, 1953-1955; 11 items (Box 10, Folder 305)
  - Loose Housing Of Dairy Calves, undated; 12 items (Box 10, Folder 306)
  - Machinery
    - Beet Top Drying, undated; 12 items (Box 10, Folder 307)
    - Combines, 1950-1964; 18 items (Box 10, Folder 308)
    - Cultivating, undated-1969; 17 items (Box 10, Folder 309)
    - Field Day-Combine Demonstration, 1954; 9 items (Box 10, Folder 310)
    - Harvesting, 1967-1969; 17 items (Box 10, Folder 311)
    - Haying, undated-1970; 10 items (Box 10, Folder 312)
    - High Pressure Sprayer, 1949; 16 items (Box 10, Folder 313)
    - Land Clearing, 1934-1950; 5 items (Box 10, Folder 314)
    - Loaders, undated; 2 items (Box 10, Folder 315)
    - Mowers, undated; 4 items (Box 10, Folder 316)
    - Pea Vine Drying, 1949-1950; 18 items (Box 10, Folder 317)
    - Planting, 1959-1971; 13 items (Box 10, Folder 318)
    - Plows, 1934-1962; 23 items (Box 10, Folder 319)
    - Processing, 1968; 1 item (Box 10, Folder 320)
    - Spreaders, 1962; 3 items (Box 10, Folder 321)
    - Terracing, 1962; 3 items (Box 10, Folder 322)
    - Tillage, undated; 13 items (Box 10, Folder 323)
    - Tractors, 1960-1974; 44 items (Box 10, Folder 324)
  - Materials Handling
    - undated (Box 11, Folder 325)
    - 1958, 21 items (Box 11, Folder 326)
  - Mechanical Hop Dryer, 1953; 5 items (Box 11, Folder 327)
  - Milking Equipment, undated; 3 items (Box 11, Folder 328)
  - Molasses Pump, undated; 3 items (Box 11, Folder 329)
  - Obsolete Combines and Tractors, 1927-undated; 10 items (Box 11, Folder 330)
  - Old Miscellaneous Project Photos, 1931-undated; 51 items (Box 11, Folder 331)
  - Orchard Equipment, undated; 6 items (Box 11, Folder 332)
  - Pea Vines
    - 1942-1949, 75 items (Box 11, Folder 333)
    - Dryer, 1949; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 334)
  - Pear Waste, undated; 5 items (Box 11, Folder 335)
  - Percy-Clark Milking Parlor, undated; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 336)
  - Pig Pen Studies, 1949-1950; 7 items (Box 11, Folder 337)
  - Plywood
    - Silo, 1953; 21 items (Box 11, Folder 338)
    - Silo Liners, undated; 3 items (Box 11, Folder 339)
  - Pneumatically Inflated Buildings, 1959-1960; 71 items (Box 11, Folder 340)
  - Poultry
    - Brooding, 1948-1955; 51 items (Box 11, Folder 341-342)
    - Cooling, 1954-undated; 13 items (Box 11, Folder 343)
    - Feeders, undated; 1 item (Box 11, Folder 344)
    - Freezing studies, undated; 10 items (Box 11, Folder 345)
    - Studies, 1954; 16 items (Box 11, Folder 346)
  - RF Energy, undated; 6 items (Box 11, Folder 347)
  - Rural Electrification, undated; 33 items (Box 11, Folder 348)
  - Silo
    - Self Feeding, 1959; 46 items (Box 11, Folder 349)
    - Filling and Roughage, undated; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 350)
  - Small Hammer Mill, 1952; 4 items (Box 11, Folder 351)
  - Soil Conservation, 1934-undated; 6 items (Box 11, Folder 352)
  - Sprinkler Irrigation Studies, 1939-undated; 30 items (Box 11, Folder 353)
  - Student Pictures, 1937-undated; 35 items (Box 11, Folder 354)
  - Students, undated; 48 items (Box 11, Folder 355)
  - Tank heaters, 1948; 6 items (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Time and Motion studies, 1952-1960; 27 items (Box 11, Folder 357)
  - Tractor Short Course, 1952; 7 items (Box 11, Folder 358)
  - Unidentified Project Photos, undated; 7 items (Box 11, Folder 359)
  - Vocational Agriculture, 1953-1956; 25 items (Box 11, Folder 360)
  - Vocational Agriculture Short Course, 1953-1956; 28 items (Box 11, Folder 361)
  - Walk-in Freezer with Package Unit, 1939-undated; 47 items (Box 11, Folder 362)
  - Washington Farm Electrification Committee
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 20 items (Box 11, Folder 363)
    - 1962 Pictures, 39 items (Box 11, Folder 364)
- Series 4. Financial Ledgers, 1932-1973
  - Department
    - Agricultural Research Center, 1960 June-1973 August; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 365)
    - Department Miscellaneous, 1963 June-1973 July; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 366)
  - Department and Experiment Station, 1949 April-1957 December; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 367)
  - Experiment Station
    - 1949 April-1949 March, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 368)
    - 1958 January -1966 June, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 369)
  - Washington Farm Electrification Committee
    - (Washington Committee on the Relationship of Electricity to Agriculture), 1932 January-1960 June; 1 item (Box 12, Folder 370)
    - 1960 July-1972 July, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 371)